malleries.com 2014-06-28

# Security & Privacy Guarantee

SHOP BY DESIGNER

**Customer Testimonials**  
I just purchased a special gift for MY birthday through Malleries, and it was a wonderful experience. I was able to find a perfect vintage Burberry clutch bag. The check out, communication and shipping was top notch. I didn't have any of the gut turning 'what if' thoughts that I have with eBay. I know that I was dealing with people who truly love genuine bags. Malleries is a fabulous site.

 _Jennie, Philli_

| 

Security & Privacy Guarantee

We appreciates your concerns regarding how your information is used and considers it a Priority to protect ALL your Personal Information. Information provided will NEVER be sold or rented to any outside party. This notice describes our privacy policy. By using the our web site you accept the practices described in this Privacy Notice.

| **Security Policy** |   |    
---|---|---  
We are committed to handling your personal information with high standards of information security. We take appropriate physical electronic and administrative steps to maintain the security and accuracy of personally identifiable information we collect, including limiting the number of people who have physical access to our database servers, as well as employing electronic security systems and password protections that guard against unauthorized access. Our website uses encryption technology, such as Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), to protect your personal information during data transport. Please note that e-mail is not encrypted and is not considered to be a secure means of transmitting credit card information.  
  |   |   
  
A closed "Lock" on the bottom right corner of your browser indicates the page you are visiting is encrypted and secure. If someone was to interrupt our communication they would see only random numbers and letters. Our customers can be confident that all personal information is secure. A closed "Lock" on the bottom right corner of your browser indicates the page you are visiting is encrypted and secure. If someone was to interrupt our communication they would see only random numbers and letters. Our customers can be confident that all personal information is secure.  
  
If you prefer you may purchase online merchandise the shop owner of the item you wish to purchase if the phone number is published. If the shop owner has opted to publish their phone number for ordering the phone number will be located on the items page. 

**Privacy Policy**  
To help us achieve our goal of providing the highest quality products and services, we have implemented procedures to ensure that your personal information is handled in a safe, secure, and responsible manner. We have posted this privacy policy in order to explain our information collection practices and the choices you have about the way information is collected and used. 

As we continue to develop our Web site and take advantage of advances in technology to improve the services we offer, this privacy policy likely will change. We therefore encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. 

  1. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to any person, violations of Malleries’ terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 
  2. We transfer information about you if Malleries is acquired by or merged with another company.

**The Information We Collect  
**When you register to buy items on the site we ask for information such as your name, address, email address, phone number, user name, credit card information and notification preferences. 

Malleries uses cookies to provide continuity from page to page. Within a single visit, these cookies store information such as your shopping list to simplify checkout.  They do not contain any personally identifiable information. To access any secure areas such as your account information, you must still enter your password. The cookie itself does not tell us who you are, your email address or anything else personal.  We use cookies to provide our visitors with a better experience on our site.

  1. We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information in order to do their jobs. 
  2. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.
  3. Your Malleries Account Information is password-protected. 
  4. In certain areas Malleries uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.

**How We Use the Information We Collect**  
We use the information we collect for various purposes, including: 

  * to complete your purchase transactions;
  * to provide the services you request;
  * to keep you informed about the status of your orders;
  * to send you our catalogs and other offerings by mail; 

**Online Account Registration  
**To make online shopping faster and easier, you may register with Malleries.com. As a registered customer, you only have to enter your shipping addresses and billing information once; they will be securely stored with us for your future use. Using your name and a password of your choice, you may access your account online at any time to add, delete, or change information. 

If you are using a public computer, we strongly encourage you to LOG OUT at the conclusion of your session. Your information will still be stored with us but it will not be accessible to anyone else from that computer. 

**E-Mails  
**You will receive promotional e-mails from us only if you have asked to receive them. If you do not want to receive email from Malleries you can click on the unsubscribe link and hit send at the bottom of any email communication sent by us. Please allow us 3 business days from when the request was received to complete the removal, as some of our promotions may already have been in process before you submitted your request.   
**  
Acceptance  
**By using this Web Site, you accept the policies set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

Copyright (c) 2006 Malleries, Inc. All rights reserved. 

Changes to this Privacy Policy  
Malleries may update this policy. All such updates shall become effective immediately. Therefore, you should review this policy from time to time when you log on to this website.
